- [gasps]
- [Debbie] Oh.
You have these striking
alabaster cheekbones.
Did you know that?
No. [sighs]
Well, you do.
They're strong.
Like you.
You're attractive, Rhonda.
Maybe not
in a conventional sense.
Your beauty
is more severe. [chuckles]
Maybe even feral,
like in a European way.
Yeah.
Let me just...
- Ow!
- Oh...
Hey. It's okay.
We're your friends.
- No one here
is going to hurt you.
- [Debbie] Yeah.
- [Susan] Okay?
- Okay.
[Debbie] Let me just
try one more time.
[♪ "Lady" playing]
[inaudible chatter]
- Oh, Rhonda.
- [chuckling] Oh.
You are stunning.
You're gonna be able to
have sex with anyone you want.
Or anyone in the band,
at least.
[Liz clicks tongue]
She's a fall, not a spring.
She'll need warmer undertones,
but I do like
what you've done with the hair.
I remember when
that homecoming queen crown
was placed atop my head
like it was yesterday.
I knew in that moment,
I had to get out
of my shithole town
and make something of myself.
My destiny was sealed
right then and there.
Someone less evolved would have
taken it as a sign to stay put.
Be a big fish in a small pond.
But not me,
I saw a ladder that led out.
I would need to win
Miss Indianapolis next,
and win and win and win
until I got
to where I am today.
A winner's psychology is...
special.
Complex.
Susan knows
what I'm talking about.
And now you do too, Rhonda.
[chuckles]
Did you know my mother
was homecoming queen too?
No.
It's a shame
the royal bloodline
has to die with me.
I'll just have to pretend
you're my daughter, Rhonda.
[Liz sighs]
This must be
what it feels like to adopt.
[inhales deeply] How tragic.
[sniffs]
- Since when
do you wear Giorgio?
- Your father got it for me.
A present for saving your skin
at school the other day.
It's very exciting. It's new.
[♪ suspenseful music plays]
Girlie smell.
[breathing shakily]
music plays]
[Bret]
The homecoming count was in.
And even though
it was meant to give us
a rare glimpse of hope,
I couldn't help but feel that
by turning Rhonda's return
into an impossible fantasy,
we'd actually handed
the victory to The Trawler.
The ballots have arrived.
Thank you, Miss Schaffer.
Hi, baby. [kisses]
- [Croft] I said thank you,
Miss Schaffer.
- Yeah.
[Croft] Candidates cannot
participate in the tally.
But since you are a female
enrolled as a senior,
you are automatically
considered a candidate.
- Leave those to us.
- But Bret is eligible
to be a candidate.
Why does he get to stay
and count?
Because Bret
has no chance at king.
We all know that.
He's impartial by default.
[Debbie sighs]
[door closes]
[Croft sighs]
- [Lydia] Principal.
- [Croft] Thank you.
Well, all right then.
Let's get started.
One for Rhonda.
One for Susan.
One for Susan. [sighs]
[yawning] Oh, my God.
- Hey.
- Is it over? Who won?
No, we're still counting.
The halfway mark.
It's so exhausting,
but it's close.
Okay. Just give me
the numbers, Bret.
I run a charity.
I need facts
that I can work with, okay?
- It's looking good for Rhonda.
- Mm-hmm.
But honestly,
it's too close to call it.
- It's neck and neck.
- [sighs]
Okay.
What about me and Susan?
Who's ahead there?
What does that matter?
Rhonda's in the lead.
Susan's right behind
Rhonda, okay?
And me?
You have one vote.
Aw. Debbie,
that make you upset?
[stammers]
I didn't think you cared.
You're not in it to win.
I know.
I was never going to win
because I never do.
Susan does.
[sighs]
This entire school thinks
that I'm a frivolous
and spiteful clown.
[scoffs]
All the charity in the world
can't change how people see me.
I don't see you like that.
Would it make you
feel any better if I told you
that one vote was from me?
No.
Because it would
be a lie, Bret.
[sniffs]
I was that one vote.
[voice breaking]
I voted for myself.
We're still counting.
[sighs]
[laughing] Mmm.
[Croft clears throat]
Thank you, Mr. Ellis,
for joining us.
Shall we resume?
- Thank you, Lydia.
- [Lydia] Mm-hmm.
One for Debbie.
Debbie.
Attention, students.
I want to quickly
interrupt your school day
to announce
this year's official
senior homecoming court
in advance
of the final crowning
of homecoming king and queen.
Your 1981 homecoming court
belongs to...
- Rhonda Fox.
- [gasps]
Susan Reynolds.
[students cheering, applause]
Debbie Schaffer.
- [gasps]
- [applause]
- Thom Wright.
- [whooping, applause]
- Ryan Gifford.
- [applause]
And Robert Mallory.
Thank you. Thank you.
Congratulations to
this year's homecoming court.
[sighs]
We look forward to crowning
the king and queen.
Well, look who it is.
- That's quite an outfit.
- They say to dress
for the job you want.
- Yeah, what job is that?
- King.
Come on, I got you something.
Come on.
You know, I thought you
didn't care about that stuff.
I don't, but I do care
about Thom losing.
[Susan] Mm-hmm.
Listen, if I do
become homecoming king,
I want you to know that
Rhonda can never be my queen.
You're my queen.
Robert, stop.
We can't.
- [chuckling] Robert,
Giorgio is not cheap.
- [chuckles]
Neither are you.
[sniffs]
Oh, it's wonderful.
What are you doing?
I want to smell like my girl.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[announcer] Everyone,
please welcome
your freshman class float.
- The Jaws of Opportunity.
[chuckles]
- [cheering]
They sure won't get swallowed
by the pressure.
All right.
Next up, we have
the sophomores'
Setting Sail
to New Destinations.
Excuse me. Thank you.
[horn honking]
Thanks so much.
Believe it or not,
the concession stand
wouldn't make you a daiquiri,
so here you go.
It's Tab with a half a flask
of rye bourbon.
[announcer]
Next, we have the junior class
with their float...
Nearly the same thing.
- [announcer]
Give My Regards to Broadway.
- [cheering, applause]
If that doesn't
razzle-dazzle you,
I don't know what does.
[scoffs]
Look at this god-awful float.
[chuckles]
Oh, you are about to
put the whole school
to shame, Steven.
- Yeah.
- I'm proud of you.
And last up,
we have the senior class
with their float.
"The Last Fantasia,
a deconstructed opera
wherein aesthetics and context
refuse the choke hold
of expectation,
heralding a 1980s
defined by mutiny of form."
- [gasps]
- [all cheering]
[student] Good job, guys!
It's a masterpiece.
You know, in your 12 years
of working for me,
I've never seen you
do one single thing right,
- but tonight, you came close.
- [sighs]
I just want us
to remember this...
[inhales deeply]
...this moment.
[announcer]
All right, everyone,
that does it for our parade...
How did Debbie pull this off?
[announcer] Next up
will be your very own...
Maybe some of me
rubbed off on her after all.
...announcing the winners
of this year's
homecoming king and queen.
I don't know.
Float's weird.
Am I the only one
who doesn't get it?
I think it's visionary.
Ferdinando Scarfiotti's
a genius.
Don't be nervous, Rhonda.
This is yours to win.
Just try to breathe.
And now, the moment
we've all been waiting for.
I'd like to welcome this year's
homecoming court to the stage.
[cheering]
Let's go, Debbie!
Here are your final nominees
for homecoming queen and king.
And with no further ado,
your homecoming queen
this year is...
[drumroll]
Susan Reynolds.
[crowd cheering]
[chuckling]
Fuck me raw. [sighs]
Fuck.
[Croft] And your
homecoming king goes to...
Robert Mallory.
[cheering]
[Robert] Guess they like
the new kid, huh?
Um...
Thank you all so much.
This means the world to me.
It really does.
But I can't accept this crown.
- [crowd gasping, muttering]
- It belongs to a true queen,
a survivor,
- and a beauty in her own right.
- [whispers]
She's gonna give it to Debbie.
I'd like to give this
to Rhonda Fox.
[cheering, applause]
- [sighs]
- [chuckling]
[chuckles]
Come on, Rhonda.
You deserve it.
[cheering, applause continues]
[sniffs]
- Susan Reynolds kidnapped me.
- What?
[crowd gasps]
[♪ dramatic music plays]
- That's not true.
- [feedback screeches]
[Rhonda gagging]
That's not true.
Rhonda, why would you say that?
[sobbing]
What are you
searching for, Bret?
A police contact.
I need to help Susan.
I wouldn't worry about Susan.
She has an alibi.
We were at my house
both of the nights that Rhonda
and Matt Kellner disappeared,
and the police already know
because I told them.
When did you tell them that?
When they took me in
and questioned me for six hours
because you told them
to look into me,
you fucking pest.
You're a little bit obsessed
with me, aren't you, Bret?
Well, you would love that,
wouldn't you?
What kind of game
are you playing, Robert?
I'm not playing a game.
I don't think about you at all.
You're invisible to me.
And that really bothers you,
doesn't it, Bret?
Well, I'm sorry
to break it to you,
but people aren't
thinking about you
nearly as much
as you think they are.
You think about me and Susan.
Don't you, Bret?
You imagine me
playing with her nipples.
Her eyes rolling back as
she feels all nine inches of me
inside her.
Do you wish
you were there with us, Bret?
Replacing me inside her?
Hoping you can lick up my come
off the floor
while we aren't looking?
Your threats
don't work on me, Robert.
I know who you really are.
You're just a sick,
little rich kid
who killed his own mommy.
Says the boy whose parents
have been in Europe
for a suspiciously long time.
Should we tell the police
to look into that?
Look under the floorboards.
Bring in the cadaver dogs.
I know them very well now.
Stop fucking with me, Bret.
Consider this
your final warning.
Don't fuck with a king.
[breathing shakily]
[electricity crackling]
[crackling continues]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[gasps, breathes shakily]
[♪ "Baby" playing]
♪♪ Yeah, I can see it ♪
♪♪ In the corner of the bar ♪
♪♪ With the really shitty art ♪
♪♪ And I'm really
Super charged ♪
♪♪ Oh, I feel it ♪
♪♪ Feel the pounding
Of your heart ♪
♪♪ Your jeans
When they get hard ♪
♪♪ Hot leather in your car ♪
♪♪ I thought I would live
With my girlfriends ♪
♪♪ And we would grow old
On a compound ♪
♪♪ I thought
I would die like a virgin ♪
♪♪ But now I'm ready to ♪
♪♪ Call you ♪
♪♪ Have your ♪
♪♪ Be your baby ♪
♪♪ Call you ♪
♪♪ Have your ♪
♪♪ Be your baby ♪
♪♪ I'm so committed ♪
♪♪ Say forever like a thread ♪
♪♪ Put the veil up on my head ♪
♪♪ Handcuff me to the bed ♪
♪♪ God is my witness ♪
♪♪ Wanna take you like an oath ♪
♪♪ Be the smoke
Inside your bowl ♪
♪♪ Be the Kool-Aid
In your cult ♪
♪♪ I thought I would live
With my girlfriends ♪
♪♪ And we would grow old
On a compound ♪
♪♪ I thought
I would die like a virgin ♪
♪♪ But now I'm ready to ♪
♪♪ Call you ♪
♪♪ Have your ♪
♪♪ Be your baby ♪
♪♪ Call you ♪
♪♪ Have your ♪
♪♪ Be your baby ♪
♪♪ Call you ♪
♪♪ Have your ♪
♪♪ Be your baby ♪
[♪ song ends]